# **Christopher Persaud-Cox**

Dedicated and adaptive individual who is highly capable of learning new skills quickly. Has 5+ years working in a fast-paced and changing environment, including just under 2 years working in a leadership role. Adept at training others to meet industry and customer standards with integrity while building a trusting customer experience. Successful in proficiently learning and understanding software programs as well as a myriad of machinery and stations necessary for efficient and productive performance.

# Chanhassen, MN, 55317 christopherp.c.2day@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Emerson**, Chanhassen, MN — *Instrument Builder 2*

July 2021 - PRESENT

- Ensure consistent flow of production at various workstations throughout the day.
- Inspect products to ensure they meet standards.
- Train team members on various machinery and workstations.
- Create reliable products that meet customer expectations.

## **Chipotle**, Chanhassen MN — *Service Manager*

Sep 2019 - May 2021

- Responsible for providing feedback to employees to improve customer satisfaction.
- Created a customer focused environment.
- Maintained clean and sanitary restaurant conditions daily.
- Monitored and documented incoming and outgoing cash flow.

## **Chipotle**, Chanhassen, MN — Kitchen Manager

Jun 2019 - Sep 2019

- Ensured upkeep of company standards.
- Oversaw food-quality standards and ensured they were met.
- Quickly delegated tasks to employees.
- Prepared establishment for business.
- Quickly adapted to unpredictable production conditions.

### **EDUCATION**

## **Performance Institute of Minnesota**, Eden Prairie, MN **High School Diploma**

Achieved a 3.6 GPA

Aug 2015 - Jun 2018

### **SKILLS**

Avid and quick learner.

Good communicator.

Familiar and comfortable with computers.

Adaptive worker.

Critical thinker and problem solver.

Works well individually or with others.

### Achievements

### **Graduated High school with honors**

Created personalized software class which included curriculum approved by school director

### Outstanding performer

received for taking as many courses as possible and showing dedication towards my major.

### Serve-safe certified

received for completing tests required to operate a restaurant.

### Soldering certified

Completed courses and training to solder within my workplace.